um the question I've been asked what
about code
academy um we don't need to go there to
see you can go look for it code academy
I've been working and monitoring code
academy since 2013 or so when it came
out and to be fair I have not looked at
code academy in the last four years I
have not actually gone through it
significantly um the short answer is it
sucks compared to your own projects um
any of the four education projects and
that includes free code Camp uh to a
limited extent I mean all of them all of
them including the the most recent one
um I won't I don't remember the name of
it Dev do
whatever um they all suffer from the
same problem and I talk about that in
another video that I just made um about
using project-based learning as
recommended by one of the best
developers on the planet TJ hollowe
Chuck um who recommends actual learning
uh using the techniques and tools that
are real that will get you a job that
will be the same thing that you'll use
on the job and So my answer for code
academy is the same as the others uh
just don't find something that you want
to do and focus on using real tools to
do that and if you want an idea for some
projects that are very real that will
have um relevance to you immediately the
rest of the boot boot camp I say boot
camp there's another video about boot
camps um the rest of the video the rest
of the stuff that we do in the beginner
boost um is based on actual projects
that will give you experience that you
are doing from scratch and don't leave
you without the skills necessary to
actually get a job or even make a web
page so some of the go watch them make
sure you watch the video about um free
code camp that I made earlier um when I
talk about 45 people going through freeo
camp and getting a certificate for web
development and not a single one being
able to make a web page same applies for
code academy uh because you're learning
an educational tool so um that's all I
have to say about that um I'm I'm sorry
I mean a fun fact actually the the guy
who invented the
platform uh the python platform for code
academy omot actually proceed to
proceeded to leave code academy and he
went on to do to form repet which is
another you know online thing and um got
you know the series a funding for that
and everything so he actually has done a
lot of stuff using containerized
backends um to make it feel like you're
doing real development on a real machine
but you're not you're you're doing it
through a web interface and there is no
business there's no job on the planet
that's going to have you doing that uh
if you're using a web interface for
something it's always going to be on the
side your main development almost always
for all major companies is going to be
used using real tools like the stuff
that we talk about in the Boost